Mahdi Mahmoudkhani

Mashhad, Razavi Khorasan, Iran

mahdi.mahmoudkhani2004@gmail.com

+989339472645

linkedin.com/in/mahdi-mahmoudkhani

Summary

I am diving into the vast world of programming and computers, driven by curiosity and a thirst for knowledge. Through exploration across various fields and gaining experiences, I am on a journey to acquire diverse technical and soft skills, ultimately aiming to discover my ideal career path therefore, with a strong commitment to growth and innovation, I'm keen to collaborate with talented teams and contribute to the development of various software solutions.

Experience



Teacher

PythonTeek Nov 2023 - Present (5 months)

Assistant

FUM Computer Science Student Society Nov 2023 - Present (5 months)

Education



Ferdowsi University of Mashhad

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science 2022 - Present

Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Go (Programming Language) • Git • C++ • Python (Programming Language) • Analytical Skills • Problem Solving • English • Communication • Leadership